Guide to Chancellor of the University of Pittsburgh, Edward H. Litchfield, Administrative Files, 1956-1965 UA.2.10.1956-1965
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Subject List, 1956-1965; I.
  - Femco, Inc. Electronic and Communication Equipment (Box 50, Folder 417)
  - Finance, Vice Chancellor for (search) (Box 50, Folder 418)
  - Finance, Acting Vice Chancellor for (Box 50, Folder 419)
  - Fine Arts, Department of (Box 50, Folder 420)
  - Forbes Avenue Relocation (Box 50, Folder 421)
  - Foreign Specialists Program, September-October 1958 (Box 50, Folder 422)
  - Foreign Specialists Program, June 1957-April 1958 (Box 50, Folder 423)
  - Foster Memorial (Box 50, Folder 424)
  - Fraternities (Box 50, Folder 425)
  - Frick Fine Arts Building, December 1962-September 1965 (Box 50, Folder 426)
  - Frick Fine Arts Building, November 1956-November 1962 (Box 51, Folder 427)
  - Frick Fine Arts Building, Correspondence concerning the use of the building (Box 51, Folder 428)
  - Frick Fine Arts Building, Frick Ground breaking (Box 51, Folder 429)
  - Frick Fine Arts Building, Frick Ground breaking - Cornerstone laying (Box 51, Folder 430)
  - Fund for the Advancement of Education (Box 51, Folder 431)
  - Fundraising, October 1964-July 1965 (Box 51, Folder 432-435)
  - Fundraising, Campaign Staff Meetings Minutes, Action Memoranda, Newsletters (Box 51, Folder 436)
  - Fundraising, Participants (Box 51, Folder 437)
  - Fundraising, Friends of the University (Box 51, Folder 438)
  - Fundraising, Friends of the University - Corporate Foundations (Box 52, Folder 439)
  - F General
    - Fabian - Farley (Box 52, Folder 440)
    - Farm - Ferguson Signature of J. Edgar Hoover (FBI) (Box 52, Folder 441)
    - Ferks - Fleischer (Box 52, Folder 442)
    - Fleming - Ford City (Box 52, Folder 443)
    - Ford Foundation - Foreign (Box 52, Folder 444)
    - Forest - Foster (Box 52, Folder 445)
    - Foundation - Fredericks (Box 53, Folder 446)
    - Fredrika - Freeman (Box 53, Folder 447)
    - Freese - Friesell (Box 53, Folder 448)
    - Frodin - Furnas (Box 53, Folder 449)
  - General Affairs, Assistant Chancellor, May 1960-September 1961, July 1963 (Box 53, Folder 450)
  - General Affairs, Assistant Chancellor, August 1956, July 1959-April 1960 (Box 53, Folder 451)
  - General Affairs, Assistant Chancellor, January 1959-June 1965 (Box 53, Folder 452)
  - General Affairs, Assistant Chancellor, January 1957-December 1958 (Box 53, Folder 453)
  - General Affairs, Assistant Chancellor, May 1956-December 1956 (Box 54, Folder 454)
  - General Studies, School of Development of Adult Education - Steering Committee (Box 54, Folder 455)
  - Geography, Department of (Box 54, Folder 456)
  - Geology, Department of (Box 54, Folder 457)
  - Germanic Languages, Department of (Box 54, Folder 458)
  - Governor's Committee of One Hundred for Better Education (Box 54, Folder 459)
  - Governor's Committee on Education, March - April 1961, October 1965, January- February 1957 (Box 54, Folder 460-461)
  - Governor's Council of Science and Technology, March 1963-October 1963 (Box 54, Folder 462-463)
  - Governor's Council of Science and Technology, October 1963-April 1964 (Box 55, Folder 464-467)
  - Governor's Council of Science and Technology, June 1964 1 Volume - Governor's Council of Science and Technology Draft of Final Report of the Governor's Council of Science and Technology, June 29, 1964 (Box 55, Folder 468)
  - Governor's Council of Science and Technology, September 1964 (Box 55, Folder 469)
  - Governor's Council of Science and Technology, September 1964 (Box 56, Folder 470)
  - Governor's Council of Science and Technology, September 1964-July 1965 (Box 56, Folder 471)
  - Gow, J. Steele, Correspondence (Box 56, Folder 472)
  - Graduate Faculty, July 1962-July 1965 (Box 56, Folder 473-476)
  - Graduate Faculty, June 1955-June 1962 (Box 57, Folder 477-482)
  - Graduate Faculty, University Council on Graduate Study (Box 57, Folder 483)
  - Graduate Faculty, Vice Chancellor of Academic Disciplines, January 1962-June 1962 (Box 58, Folder 484-485)
  - Graduate and Professional Education for Women, Committee on (Box 58, Folder 486)
  - Greensburg Campus Includes maps of Greensburg and Westmoreland County, Lynch Estate (Box 58, Folder 487)
  - Guatemala, July 1963-June 1965 (Box 58, Folder 488-489)
  - Guatemala, December 1962-June 1963 (Box 59, Folder 490)
  - G General
    - Gable (Box 59, Folder 491)
    - Gaddis - Geiger (Box 59, Folder 492)
    - Gemassmer - Gillin (Box 59, Folder 493)
    - Gilmore - Good (Box 59, Folder 494)
    - Goodale - Gratz (Box 59, Folder 495)
    - Graves - Griggs (Box 59, Folder 496)
    - Grimes - Guzzardi (Box 59, Folder 497)
  - Health Center, 1959-1965 (Box 60, Folder 498-500)
  - Health Center Up to Date Review of the Health Center, November 1964 (Box 60, Folder 501)
  - Health Center, Agreements of Affiliation (Box 60, Folder 502)
  - Health Center, Proposed Capitol Improvement Program (Box 60, Folder 503)
  - Health Center, Proposed Capitol Improvement Program, Report (Box 60, Folder 504)
  - Health Center, Joint Administrators Committee (Box 61, Folder 505)
  - Health Center, Joint Trustees Committee, 1958-1965 (Box 61, Folder 506-509)
  - Health Center, Steering Committee (Box 61, Folder 510)
  - Health Center, Campaign, 1962-1964 (Box 61, Folder 511)
  - Health Center, Campaign, 1960-1961 (Box 61, Folder 512)
  - Health Center, 1959 (Box 62, Folder 513)
  - Health Center, Strategy (Box 62, Folder 514)
  - Health Center, Special Study Committee (Box 62, Folder 515)
  - Health, Education, and Welfare, U.S. Department of Health (Box 62, Folder 516)
  - Health, Education, and Welfare, U.S. Department of - Education, Nationale Defence Education Act, 1962-1965 (Box 62, Folder 517)
  - Health, Education, and Welfare, U.S. Department of Education 1958 - 1963 (Box 62, Folder 518)
  - Health Professions, Vice Chancellor of, January 1961-April 1965 (Box 62, Folder 519-520)
  - Health Professions, Vice Chancellor of, April 1956-December 1960 (Box 63, Folder 521-527)
  - Health Professions, Vice Chancellor of, April 1950-March 1956 (Box 64, Folder 528-530)
  - Health Professions, Board of Visitors (Box 64, Folder 531)
  - History, Department of, August 1955-May 1965 (Box 64, Folder 532-533)
  - History, Department of, Colodny Case, June 1961-December 1962 (Box 64, Folder 534-535)
  - History, Department of, Colodny Case, June 1961 (Box 65, Folder 536)
  - History, Department of, Colodny Case File of reactions concerning letter to Mr. Price (Box 65, Folder 537)
  - History, Department of, Colodny Case, January 1961-May 1961 (Box 65, Folder 538)
  - History, Department of, Colodny Case Comments on Colodny Report (Box 65, Folder 539)
  - Honorary Degrees, 1962-1965 (Box 65, Folder 540)
  - Honorary Degrees, 1955-1959 (Box 65, Folder 541)
  - Hospital Council of Western Pennsylvania (Box 65, Folder 542)
  - Hospital Planning Association of Allegheny County (Box 65, Folder 543)
  - Hospitals, Parking Garage, Expansion West (Box 65, Folder 544)
  - Hospitals, Children's Hospital (Box 65, Folder 545)
  - Hospitals, Eye and Ear Hospital (Box 65, Folder 546)
  - Hospitals, Large 9, 1963-1964 (Box 65, Folder 547)
  - Hospitals, Large 9, Indigent Patient Committee, 1960-1962 (Box 66, Folder 548)
  - Hospitals, Magee Women's Hospital (Box 66, Folder 549)
  - Hospitals, Presbyterian-University Hospital, July 1963 - 1965 (Box 66, Folder 550-553)
  - Hospitals, Presbyterian-University Hospital, January 1958-June 1963 (Box 67, Folder 554-561)
  - Human Relations Center (Box 67, Folder 562)
  - Humanities, Division of (Box 68, Folder 563)
  - H General
    - Habley - Harcourts (Box 68, Folder 564)
    - Hardin - Hathorn (Box 68, Folder 565)
    - Hauge - Heald (Box 68, Folder 566)
    - Health - Heart (Box 68, Folder 567)
    - Hechinger - Henderson (Box 68, Folder 568)
    - Heneman - Historical (Box 68, Folder 569)
    - Hobbing - Hontas (Box 69, Folder 570)
    - Hood - Hull 2 Signatures of J. Edgar Hoover (Box 69, Folder 571)
    - Human - Hunt 1 Signature of Hubert H. Humphrey (Vice President of U.S.) (Box 69, Folder 572)
    - Huskey - Hvozdovich (Box 69, Folder 573)
  - ICA Faculty Rotation (Box 69, Folder 574)
  - Inauguration, Inaugural Address (Box 69, Folder 575)
  - Inauguration, Participants in Procession (Box 69, Folder 576)
  - Inauguration, Invitations (Box 69, Folder 577)
  - Inauguration, Inaugural Expenses (Box 69, Folder 578)
  - Industrial Civilization (Box 69, Folder 579)
  - Information Service, Office of, 1959-1964 (Box 70, Folder 580-581)
  - Industrial Planning, Director of, January 1960-September 1961 (Box 70, Folder 582-584)
  - Industrial Planning, Director of, July 1959-December 1959 (Box 71, Folder 585)
  - Interdisciplinary Committee (Box 71, Folder 586)
  - International Dimensions (Box 71, Folder 587)
  - International Press Institute (Box 71, Folder 588)
  - International Press Institute, Tour (Box 71, Folder 589)
  - International Political Science Association (IPSA), June 1958-August 1964 (Box 71, Folder 590)
  - International Political Science Association (IPSA), September157 - May 1958 (Box 71, Folder 591)
  - International Political Science Association (IPSA) Program, September 10 - 13, 1957 (Box 71, Folder 592)
  - International Political Science Association (IPSA), January 1956-August 1957 (Box 72, Folder 593-595)
  - International Political Science Association (IPSA) Material for Meeting (Box 72, Folder 596)
  - International Political Science Association (IPSA) Geneva trip (Box 72, Folder 597)
  - I General
    - IBM - Indiana (Box 72, Folder 598)
    - Indonesia - Insurance (Box 72, Folder 599)
    - Intercollegiate - International (Box 72, Folder 600)
    - Inter-university - Iwasa (Box 73, Folder 601)
  - Johnstown Campus, 1955 - 1965 (Box 73, Folder 602-605)
  - Joint Appointments and Projects (Box 73, Folder 606)
  - Joint State Government Commission Higher Education In Pennsylvania, January 2, 1959 (Box 73, Folder 607)
  - Joint State Government Commission Advisory Panel Study on Advanced Training, December 17, 1958 (Box 74, Folder 608)
  - Joint State Government Commission Advisory Panel Study on Advanced Training, November 1, 1958, November 26, 1958 (Box 74, Folder 609)
  - Joint State Government Commission Advisory Panel Study on Advanced Training, October 1, 1958 (Box 74, Folder 610)
  - Joint State Government Commission, March 1958-February 1962 (Box 74, Folder 611-613)
  - Joint State Government Commission, March 1958-June 1958 (Box 75, Folder 614)
  - J General
    - Jackson - Johns (Box 75, Folder 615)
    - Johnson - Junior (Box 75, Folder 616)
  - Knowledge Availability Systems (KAS) Lewis Research Conference, October 29, 1964 (Box 75, Folder 617)
  - Knowledge Availability Systems (KAS), 1960-1965 (Box 75, Folder 618-620)
  - Knowledge Availability Systems (KAS) Electronic Information Handling Conference, 1964 (Box 76, Folder 621)
  - Koslov Dinner, July 10, 1959 (Box 76, Folder 622)
  - Krushchev Luncheon,Program, Speeches, Guest List, September 24, 1959 (Box 76, Folder 623)
  - Krushchev Luncheon, Correspondence, September 24, 1959 (Box 76, Folder 624)
  - Krushchev Luncheon, Thank You Notes, September 24, 1959 (Box 76, Folder 625)
  - K General
    - Kahn - KDKA (Box 76, Folder 626)
    - Kearney - Ketterer (Box 76, Folder 627)
    - Khayyat - Kuznik (Box 76, Folder 628)
  - Langley Hall Dedication, November 11, 1961 (Box 77, Folder 629)
  - Latin America, JUne 1962-October 1964 (Box 77, Folder 630-632)
  - Latin American Operations, Special Assistant to the Chancellor for (Box 77, Folder 633)
  - Latin American Studies, Center for (Box 77, Folder 634)
  - Law, School of, 1955-1965 (Box 77, Folder 635-637)
  - Law, School of, Friends of the Law School (Box 77, Folder 638)
  - Law, School of, Dr. A. C. Van Dusen (Box 78, Folder 639)
  - Leader Exchange Program (Box 78, Folder 640)
  - Learning Research and Development Center (Box 78, Folder 641)
  - Legal Research Foundation (Box 78, Folder 642)
  - Legislature Dinner, February 26, 1965 (Box 78, Folder 643)
  - Legislator's Luncheon, November 29, 1960 (Box 78, Folder 644)
  - Levitt, Irving F. (Box 78, Folder 645)
  - Liberal Arts, School of, Office of the Dean, January 1958-March 1965 (Box 78, Folder 646-647)
  - Liberal Arts, School of, Office of the Dean, July 1955-December 1957 (Box 79, Folder 648-650)
  - Library (Hillman), August 1955-May 1965 (Box 79, Folder 651-654)
  - Library (Hillman), Ground breaking (Box 79, Folder 655)
  - Library and Information Sciences, Graduate School of (Box 79, Folder 656)
  - Local Government, Institute of (Box 80, Folder 657)
  - Log (listing activities by date), January 2, 1959-December 30, 1959 (Box 80, Folder 658-660)
  - Log, January 2, 1960-December 30, 1960 (Box 80, Folder 661-662)
  - Log, January 3, 1961-December 29, 1961 (Box 81, Folder 663-664)
  - Log, January 2, 1962-May 31, 1963 (Box 81, Folder 665-668)
  - Log, June 1, 1963-December 30, 1963 (Box 82, Folder 669-671)
  - Log, December 30, 1963-October 1, 1964 (Box 82, Folder 672-674)
  - Log, April 6, 1964-October 1, 1964 (Box 82, Folder 673-674)
  - Log, October 1, 1964-May 28, 1965 (Box 83, Folder 675-678)
  - L General
    - Labarth - Lectures (Box 83, Folder 679)
    - Lederle - Liberal (Box 83, Folder 680)
    - Library - Litkenhous (Box 83, Folder 681)
    - Little - Louden (Box 84, Folder 682)
    - Lowy - Lyttle (Box 84, Folder 683)
  - Mc General
    - McCall, Dr. Milton L. (Director of Personell) (Box 84, Folder 684)
    - McCormack Interview (Box 84, Folder 685)
    - McAllister - McDowell (Box 84, Folder 686)
    - McElroy - McTighe (Box 84, Folder 687)
  - Maps (Box 84, Folder 688)
  - Martin, Park H. (Physical Education Plant) (Box 84, Folder 689)
  - Master Plan for Higher Education in Pennsylvania (Box 84, Folder 690)
  - Mathematics, Department of (Box 84, Folder 691)
  - Medicine, School of, September 1955-June 1965 (Box 85, Folder 692-698)
  - Medicine, School of Advisory Committee on the Organization of an Institute for Experimental Medicine (Box 86, Folder 699)
  - Medicine, School of Advisory Committee on the Organization of an Institute for Experimental Medicine, Transcript of Meeting: February 5, 1958 (Box 86, Folder 700)
  - Meetings, Use of University Facilities for (Box 86, Folder 701)
  - Mellon, The A.W. Trust (Box 86, Folder 702)
  - Mellon Institute, 1955-1965 (Box 86, Folder 703-704)
  - MPC Corporation: Mellon Institute, University of Pittsburgh, Carnegie Institute of Technology, January 1965-December 1965 (Box 86, Folder 705)
  - MPC Corporation: Mellon Institute, University of Pittsburgh, Carnegie Institute of Technology Proposal for Applied Materials Research Center, February 12, 1965 (Box 86, Folder 706)
  - MPC Corporation: Mellon Institute, University of Pittsburgh, Carnegie Institute of Technology, July 1964-December 1964 (Box 87, Folder 707)
  - MPC Corporation: Mellon Institute, University of Pittsburgh, Carnegie Institute of Technology, January 1964-June 1964 (Box 87, Folder 708)
  - MPC Corporation: Mellon Institute, University of Pittsburgh, Carnegie Institute of Technology Plan for Development of a Rail Commuter Demonstration Test System, 1964 (Box 87, Folder 709)
  - MPC Corporation: Mellon Institute, University of Pittsburgh, Carnegie Institute of Technology, 3 Volumes - MPC Corporation: Mellon Institute, University of Pittsburgh, Carnegie Institute of Technology Proposal for Applied Materials Research Center, March 26, 1963, January 1963-December 1963 (Box 87, Folder 710)
  - MPC Corporation: Mellon Institute, University of Pittsburgh, Carnegie Institute of Technology, July 1962-December 1962 (Box 88, Folder 711)
  - Mellon Professorships (Box 88, Folder 712)
  - Men's Debating Association (Box 88, Folder 713)
  - Microbiology, Department of (Box 88, Folder 714)
  - Middle States Association, 1955-1965 (Box 88, Folder 715-719)
  - Middle States Evaluation Meeting, November 8 - 11, 1960 (Box 89, Folder 720-721)
  - Military Government School (possible plans for) (Box 89, Folder 722)
  - Military Science and Tactics, Department of, 1955-1965 (Box 89, Folder 723-724)
  - Modern Languages, Department of (Box 89, Folder 725)
  - Morewood Close (Box 89, Folder 726)
  - Morewood Heights (Box 89, Folder 727)
  - Municipal Hospital (Box 89, Folder 728)
  - Music, Department of (Box 89, Folder 729)
  - M General
    - Mabon - Magee (Box 89, Folder 730)
    - Mager - Marquez (Box 90, Folder 731)
    - Marquis - Matteson (Box 90, Folder 732)
    - Mattusch - Mellott (Box 90, Folder 733)
    - Memorial - Michigan (Box 90, Folder 734)
    - Mid-Atlantic - Miller (Box 90, Folder 735)
    - Millsap - Moore Box 91 (Box 90, Folder 736)
    - Moorhead - Morgen (Box 91, Folder 737)
    - Moriarty - Myers (Box 91, Folder 738)
  - National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA), August 1962-July 1965 (Box 91, Folder 739-743)
  - National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA), April 1962-July 1962 (Box 92, Folder 744)
  - NASA/Industry/University Project (Box 92, Folder 745)
  - Nationality Rooms Program, June 1956-May 1965 (Box 92, Folder 746-747)
  - Natural Sciences, Dean of, January 1957-July 1965 (Box 92, Folder 748-750)
  - Natural Sciences, Dean of, August 1955-December 1956 (Box 93, Folder 751)
  - Natural Sciences, Dean of Proposal to the National Science Foundation for a Five Year Science Development Program at the University of Pittsburgh (Box 93, Folder 752)
  - Natural Sciences Quadrangle (Box 93, Folder 753)
  - Newcomer's Tea (Box 93, Folder 754)
  - Newspapers, Pittsburgh Post-Gazette, Press, Sun-Telegraph (Box 93, Folder 755)
  - Non-faculty Personnel Advisory Committee (Box 93, Folder 756)
  - Nursing, School of (Box 93, Folder 757)
  - Nursing, School of, Committee on Nursing Education (Box 93, Folder 758)
  - Nursing, School of, Search Committee, Dean of Nursing (Box 93, Folder 759)
  - Nursing, School of Glenna Walters Mars, Professor of Nursing, 1955-1957 (Box 93, Folder 760)
  - Nursing, School of Glenna Walters Mars, Professor of Nursing, 1954 (Box 93, Folder 761)
  - N General
    - Narbrit - National Civil (Box 93, Folder 762)
    - National Collegiate - National Commission (Box 93, Folder 763)
    - National Conference - National Football (Box 94, Folder 764)
    - National Forensic - National Scholarship (Box 94, Folder 765)
    - National Science (Box 94, Folder 766)
    - National Strategy - Negley (Box 94, Folder 767)
    - Neiburg - New York University (Box 94, Folder 768)
    - New York World's Fair - Norris (Box 94, Folder 769)
    - North Carolina (Box 95, Folder 770)
    - Northwest - Nyquist (Box 95, Folder 771)
  - Oakland Corporation, May 1962-December 1963 (Box 95, Folder 772-775)
  - Oakland Corporation, August 1961 pril 1962 (Box 96, Folder 776-777)
  - Oakland Corporation, August 1961-February 1962 (Box 96, Folder 777)
  - Oakland Corporation, Board Meetings, March 1965 - March 1963 (Box 96, Folder 778-783)
  - Oakland Corporation, Panther Hollow, April 1963-May 1965 (Box 97, Folder 784-787)
  - Oakland Corporation, Landscaping Project (Box 97, Folder 788)
  - Oakland Corporation, Prudential Meeting, January 22, 1962 (Box 97, Folder 789)
  - Oakland Corporation, Release Comments (Box 97, Folder 790)
  - Oakland Corporation, Research and Development (Box 97, Folder 791)
  - Oceanography, January 1964-December 1965 (Box 98, Folder 792-794)
  - Oceanography, Literature (Box 98, Folder 795)
  - Operations Research (Box 98, Folder 796)
  - Organizational Changes (Box 98, Folder 797)
  - Organization Charts and Manual, 1960, 1963-1964 (Box 98, Folder 798-800)
  - Organization Charts and Manual, copy 1-2, 1958 (Box 99, Folder 801-802)
  - O General
    - Oak - Ohio (Box 99, Folder 803)
    - Oklahoma - Ordnance (Box 99, Folder 804)
    - Oregon - Oxman (Box 99, Folder 805)
  - Pace College (Box 99, Folder 806)
  - Parking (Box 99, Folder 807)
  - Patent Policy, Advisory Committee on (Box 99, Folder 808)
  - Peace Corps,, Washington, D.C., June 24, 1961 (Box 99, Folder 809)
  - Pennsylvania Association of Colleges and Universities, 1956-1961 (Box 100, Folder 810-811)
  - Pennsylvania, Commonwealth of (Box 100, Folder 812)
  - Pennsylvania State University (Penn State) (Box 100, Folder 813)
  - Pennsylvania, University of (Box 100, Folder 814)
  - Personnel Director, 1958-1965 (Box 100, Folder 815-817)
  - Personnel Director, 1955-1957 (Box 101, Folder 818)
  - Personnel - Openings, Appointments, Proposals, 1955-1956 (Box 101, Folder 819-820)
  - Pharmacy, School of (Box 101, Folder 821)
  - Philosophy, Department of (Box 101, Folder 822)
  - Physical Education, Department of (Box 101, Folder 823)
  - Physical Plant, Director of, 1960-1965 (Box 101, Folder 824-826)
  - Physical Plant, Director of, 1955-1959 (Box 102, Folder 827-831)
  - Physics, Department of (Box 102, Folder 832)
  - Pitt Associates (Box 102, Folder 833)
  - Pitt-Penn-Temple Meetings (University of Pittsburgh, University of Pennsylvania, Temple University) (Box 102, Folder 834)
  - Pitt-Wildwood Club, 1959-1960 (Box 103, Folder 835)
  - Pitt-Wildwood Club, 1957-1958 (Box 103, Folder 836)
  - Pittsburgh Institutions (Box 103, Folder 837)
  - Pittsburgh, Project Proposals (Box 103, Folder 838)
  - Pittsburgh Bicentennial Association Executive and General Committees (Box 103, Folder 839)
  - Pittsburgh Bicentennial Association Finance Committee and Budget (Box 103, Folder 840)
  - Pittsburgh Bicentennial Association Education Committee (Box 103, Folder 841)
  - Pittsburgh Bicentennial Association Miscellaneous Committees (Box 103, Folder 842)
  - Pittsburgh Bicentennial Convocation (Box 103, Folder 843)
  - Pittsburgh Regional Planning Association AA Plan for Pittsburgh's Cultural District - Oakland" (Box 104, Folder 844)
  - Placement Advisory Committee (Box 104, Folder 845)
  - Planning and Development, Assistant Chancellor, January 1959-April 1965 (Box 104, Folder 846-850)
  - Planning and Development, Assistant Chancellor, May 1955-December 1958 (Box 105, Folder 851-854)
  - Planning and Development, Assistant Chancellor, Special Committee (Box 105, Folder 855)
  - Planning and Development, Assistant Chancellor Pitt Research Institute Promotional Report (Box 105, Folder 856)
  - Planning and Development, Advisory Committee (Box 105, Folder 857)
  - Planning and Development, Advisory Committee, Brochure (Box 105, Folder 858)
  - Planning and Development, Advisory Committee Letters from Corporations (Box 105, Folder 859)
  - Planning and Development, Center of Planning and Urban Development (Box 105, Folder 860)
  - Planning and Development, Gift Reports, April 1963-February 1964 (Box 106, Folder 861)
  - Planning and Development, Gift Reports, October 1962-March 1963 (Box 106, Folder 862)
  - Planning and Development, Report of Committee on Public Administrative Planning (Box 106, Folder 863)
  - Planning and Development, Montgomery, Edison, 1959-1963 (Box 106, Folder 864)
  - Planning and Development, Montgomery, Edison, 1956-1958 (Box 106, Folder 865)
  - Planning and Development, Stophlet, Donald V. (Box 106, Folder 866)
  - Police Department (Box 106, Folder 867)
  - Polio Vaccine Program (Box 106, Folder 868)
  - Political Science Department of, May 1960-June 1965 (Box 106, Folder 869)
  - Political Science Department of, November 1955-April 1960 (Box 107, Folder 870)
  - Population (Box 107, Folder 871)
  - Professional Schools Quadrangle (Box 107, Folder 872)
  - Professions, Vice Chancellor of, February 196 July 1965 (Box 107, Folder 873-877)
  - Professions, Vice Chancellor of, August 1956-January 1961 (Box 108, Folder 878-884)
  - Psychology, Department of (Box 109, Folder 885)
  - Public Health, Graduate School of, Auguest 1955 February 1965 (Box 109, Folder 886-888)
  - Public Instruction, Department of (Box 109, Folder 889)